Inventory of the Garland R. Farmer papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Minutes of staff meetings, 1962 July - 1963 March (Box-folder 37: 5)
- Garland R. Farmer correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 37: 6)
- NIOC [National Iron Ore Company] Board, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 37: 7)
- Early NIOC Board meetings, 1965 (Box-folder 37: 8)
- NIOC - articles of incorporation, by-laws, 1959 (Box-folder 37: 9)
- Mano-NIOC concession, 1959-1967 (Box-folder 37: 10)
- NIOC Board meeting, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 11)
- [Liberia Mining Company film materials], 1958-1960 (Box-folder 38: 1)
- Liberian history, culture, 1959-1973 (Box-folder 38: 2)
- Liberian churches, religions, 1948-1988 (Box-folder 38: 3)
- Liberian general information, 1970 (Box-folder 38: 4)
- J. M. Weeks, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 38: 5)
- Shad, Jr. [W. V. S. Tubman, Jr.], 1961-1972 (Box-folder 38: 6)
- S. A. Tolbert, 1972-1987 (Box-folder 38: 7)
- W. R. Tolbert III, 1986 (Box-folder 38: 8)
- A. B. Tolbert, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 38: 9)
- C. D. S. [Charles Dunbar Sherman]/G. R. F. [Garland R. Farmer], 1965-1969 (Box-folder 38: 10)
- [Books on Liberian culture and economy], 1968-1983 (Box-folder 38: 11)
- Contributions - past, made, or pledged, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 39: 1)
- Lansdell K. Christie miscellaneous correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 39: 2)
- L. K. C. [Lansdell K. Christie]/G. R. F. [Garland R. Farmer] correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 39: 3)
- Lansdell K. Christie correspondence, 1959-1965 (Box-folder 39: 4)
- LMC [Liberian Mining Company] news, 1964-1978 (Box-folder 39: 5)
- L. K. C. Fund, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 39: 6)
- L. K. C. - articles and photos, 1965-1988 (Box-folder 39: 7)
- Tribal affairs, history, 1966-1986 (Box-folder 39: 8)
- Liberia - miscellaneous human interest, 1966-1979 (Box-folder 39: 9)
- Zambia - economy (no. Rhodesia), 1965-1975 (Box-folder 40: 1)
- Zaire, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 40: 2)
- Tunisia geological map, undated (Box-folder 40: 3)
- Nigeria (economy), 1961-1965 (Box-folder 40: 4)
- Nigeria, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 40: 5)
- Contributions, loans, scholarships (Ben Kahn), 1966-1969 (Box-folder 40: 6)
- Nigeria, 1961-1984 (Box-folder 41: 1)
- Nigeria (general), 1966-1969 (Box-folder 41: 2)
- Nigeria documents, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 41: 3)
- Duplicates for Hoover, 1965-1985 (Box-folder 41: 4)
- Mano reports and correspondence, 1966 July-December (Box-folder 42: 1)
- Correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder 42: 2)
- Expense accounts, 1967 (Box-folder 42: 3)
- Mano - reports and correspondence, 1966 January-June (Box-folder 42: 4)
- Inventory of American aid to education in Africa, 1962 (Box-folder 42: 5)
- Atlas of African industry, 1989 (Box-folder 42: 6)
- Morocco, 1970s (Box-folder 42: 7)
- Niger, 1970s (Box-folder 42: 8)
- Mano reports - 1st half, 1969 (Box-folder 43: 1)
- Mano reports and correspondence, 1968 July-December (Box-folder 43: 2)
- Correspondence, 1967 October - 1968 September (Box-folder 43: 3)
- Mano reports and correspondence - 1st half, 1968 (Box-folder 43: 4)
- Correspondence, 1968 (Box-folder 43: 5)
- Correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 43: 6)
- Mano reports and correspondence, 1967 July-December (Box-folder 43: 7)
- Mano reports and correspondence, 1967 January-June (Box-folder 43: 8)
- NIOC [National Iron Ore Company] - LMC [Liberian Mining Company] - reports, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 43: 9)
- Mano - first cargo, undated (Box-folder 44: 1)
- Correspondence, 1969 (Box-folder 44: 2)
- Mano reports - 2nd half, 1969 (Box-folder 44: 3)
- Central American vs. African, 1968 (Box-folder 44: 4)
- Ghana - Guinea - Mali Union, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 44: 5)
- African Cooperation - general, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 44: 6)
- Organization of African Unity (OAU), 1961-1963 (Box-folder 44: 7)
- Sanniquellie Conference, 1959-1986 (Box-folder 44: 8)
- Pre-organization of African Unity meetings, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 44: 9)
- Liberian policies and proposals regarding African unity, Organization of African Unity, etc., 1962-1973 (Box-folder 44: 10)
- Mano River Union, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 44: 11)
- Van Nordheim - 1st half, 1962 (Box-folder 44: 12)
- Economic Community of West African States, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 44: 13)
- Report - Economic Integration in West Africa, 1965 (Box-folder 45: 1)
- OCAM [Afro-Mauritian Common Organization] and UAM [African and Malagasy Union], 1963-1974 (Box-folder 45: 2)
- UDEAC [Customs and Economic Union of Central Africa]-UDOA (Central Africa), 1960-1968 (Box-folder 45: 3)
- Commonwealth - Africa, EFTA, 1950-1965 (Box-folder 45: 4)
- All-Africa People's Conference, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 45: 5)
- Non-Aligned Conference, 1964-1973 (Box-folder 45: 6)
- Organization of African Unity resolutions, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 45: 7)
- Monrovia Group (pre OAU), 1961 (Box-folder 45: 8)
- Africa cooperation - Organization of African Unity cooperation, 1963-1983 (Box-folder 45: 9)
- School prospectus, 1986 (Box-folder 46: 1)
- Report - Economic Integration in West Africa, 1965 (Box-folder 46: 2)
- African cooperation, 1960-1987 (Box-folder 46: 3)
- African development research, 1960 (Box-folder 46: 4)
- Proposals for West African cooperation, undated (Box-folder 46: 5)
- Africa cooperation - health, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 46: 6)
- Africa regional cooperation - rivers, lakes, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 46: 7)
- Africa cooperation - transportation, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 46: 8)
- United Nations/African cooperation, 1963-1975 (Box-folder 46: 9)
- West Africa Francophone cooperation, 1968-1983 (Box-folder 46: 10)
- Cooperation - Maghreb, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 46: 11)
- West Africa cooperation - free trade agreements, pre ECOWAS [Economic Community of West African States], 1963-1967 (Box-folder 46: 12)
- West Africa, Economics Cooperation Organization, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 46: 13)
- West Africa Rice Development Association, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 46: 14)
- Africa cooperation, communications/press, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 46: 15)
- Africa cooperation, education, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 46: 16)
- Lebanese in Africa (excluding Liberia), 1982-1985 (Box-folder 47: 1)
- Aid to Africa - general, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 47: 2)
- Agriculture - Africa, general, 1965-1982 (Box-folder 47: 3)
- Agriculture - projects in Africa (excluding Ghana), 1961-1973 (Box-folder 47: 4)
- A. Bureau, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 47: 5)
- Bie - current, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 47: 6)
- Nkrumah speeches, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 47: 7)
- Bie Mountains, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 47: 8)
- Mano top personnel, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 47: 9)
- Bie - Garland R. Farmer, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 48: 1)
- Comp. indigenization/nationalization, 1974 (Box-folder 48: 2)
- "Africanization," expatriates of personnel, 1963-1982 (Box-folder 48: 3)
- "Africanization" of ownership, 1970-1987 (Box-folder 48: 4)
- Diamonds, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 48: 5)
- Private investment in Africa, 1969 (Box-folder 48: 6)
- Minerals - general, 1964-1974 (Box-folder 48: 7)
- African economy - general, 1966-1982 (Box-folder 48: 8)
- Industries in Africa - general, 1961-1981 (Box-folder 48: 9)
- Comp. investment - incentives/restrictions, 1967-1985 (Box-folder 48: 10)
- Assorted slides from Mano, 1970s (Box-folder 49: 1)
- Mano photographs (contract signing), 1970s (Box-folder 49: 2)
- G. R. F. [Garland R. Farmer] separation from MMAL [Mine Management Associates, Ltd.]/AMS, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 49: 3)
- National Iron Ore Company Board/reports re Mano II, 1974 (Box-folder 49: 4)
- MMAL Board, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 49: 5)
- Japanese - Bie, 1973 (Box-folder 49: 6)
- Current Ore market information - CAEMI International, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 49: 7)
- Port authority - Mano and port, 1972 (Box-folder 49: 8)
- J. J. P. [James (Jim) J. Pirtle]/Bea Mountains Company, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 49: 9)
- Ghana - names (at time of Ejurah farm work) - government officials, business personalities, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 49: 10)
- Bie Mountains, joint venture, 1970 (Box-folder 49: 11)
- Bie Mountains, BSC [British Steel Corporation], etc., 1974 (Box-folder 49: 12)
- Bie Mountains, early correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 49: 13)
- LEL [Liberian Enterprises, Ltd.], 1961-1989 (Box-folder 50: 1)
- GNMC [Ghana National Manganese Corporation] - manganese market, 1983 (Box-folder 50: 2)
- MMAL [Mine Management Associates, Ltd]. - miscellaneous, 1973 (Box-folder 50: 3)
- MMAL - management contract articles of incorporation, 1958-1971 (Box-folder 50: 4)
- G. R. F. [Garland R. Farmer] (personal)-V. R. Y. L. [Vernon R. Y. Lynn] re MMAL/AMS, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 50: 5)
- NIOC [National Iron Ore Company]-CAEMI International sales agency agreement, 1972-1982 (Box-folder 50: 6)
- Technical assistance - NIOC/MMAL-LMC [Liberian Mining Company], 1963-1974 (Box-folder 50: 7)
- Iron ore sales contracts, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 50: 8)
- Labor disputes, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 51: 1)
- NIOC/government reports, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 51: 2)
- Liberian matters at Mano, etc., 1966-1969 (Box-folder 51: 3)
- Liberian Enterprises ledger sheets - duplicates, 1970s (Box-folder 51: 4)
- LEL Board, 1958-1973 (Box-folder 51: 5)
- LEL, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 51: 6)
- Liberian Enterprises (including Wust speech), 1958-1967 (Box-folder 51: 7)
- William R. Tolbert, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 51: 8)
- Liberian relations (non-government/non-employee), 1966-1969 (Box-folder 51: 9)
- Foreign advisory, 1956-1969 (Box-folder 51: 10)
- Conferences of Heads of African and Malagasy States, 1961 (Box-folder 51: 11)